Guide to the Reston Reflections oral history collection, 1994-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Transcripts, 1994-2008; (79 boxes)
  - Welsh, Eileen, December 13, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    454.22
  - Wengert, Vicki, January 16, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    454.23
  - Wendell, Sue and Sue Schram, April 15, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    516.4
  - Westfall, Julie, June 3, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Wetzel, John, May 11, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - White (Dr.), 2000s (Box 74, Folder 18)
    506.34
  - White (Dr.), May 22, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Whitley, Grant, May 22, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Whitmoyer, Judy, January 1, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    454.24
  - Whyte, Bonnie, June 2, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Witcha, Carmen Gloria, December 7, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    454.25
  - Wilhelm, Jane, December 15, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    454.28
  - Wilkins, Tom, May 6, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Wilkens, Susan, January 9, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    506.35
  - Williams, S.D., April 22, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Ed, January 18, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    506.36
  - Williams, Carol, May 23, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    454.26
  - Wilson, Elizabeth, December 21, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    454.27
  - Wilson, 2000s (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Wilson, Kerrie, 2000s (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Wilson, Mark, June 1, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Wilson, Kerrie, June 9, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Wines, Marcia, June 1, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Wingert, Vicky, May 7, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Wingert, Vicky, 2000s (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Wingert, Vicky, June 13, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    514.25
  - Wingert, Vern, May 7, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Wingert, Victoria, January 15, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    506.37
  - Wingert, Vicky, June 3, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Witherford, Vivian, December 26, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    454.29
  - Wolfe, David, April 14, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    516.27
  - Woodruff, Jamie, April 6, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    515.14
  - Woods, Kris, January 1, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    454.30
  - Wright, Bruce, June 6, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    514.26
  - Wyn, Francis, June 2, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Yarborngbe, Kirby, June 1, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Yarbrough, Edith, January 15, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    506.38
  - Yen, Joan, May 3, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Young, Shaggy, May 11, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Young, Robert, June 9, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    514.27
  - Zablotney, Gene, June 7, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Zablotney, Gene (Mrs.), May 9, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Zaczek, Barbara, May 17, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Zamola, Pilar, June 10, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Zeile, Janet, May 25, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Zeile, Janet, June 9, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Zeile, Janet, June 9, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Zeiman, Carl, April 22, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    517.23
  - Zhang, June 5, 2008 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Zink, Paul, April 29, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    512.2
  - Zoeter, Mary, January 18, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    506.39
  - Zora, Kathy, May 4, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Zurowski, Rudolph, May 4, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Series 2: Audiotapes, 1994-2000; (11 boxes)
  These are the audiotape cassettes that have been removed from the transcripts. The audiotapes are the actual interviews conducted by the students. The audiotapes are from the oral histories that were previously processed and are the earlier interviews done by the students of Langston Hughes Middle Schools.
  - Adams, Hebron, December 9, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Alcorn, Dan, May 24, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Robin, May 16, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Aloanso, Leo, December 15, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Aman, Bill, January 24, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Ames, Priscilla, January 14, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Ames, Priscilla, December 2, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Amos (Mrs.), 2000s (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Avjean, Ruth, January 26, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Barber, Deborah, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Baropox, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Barry, David, June 13, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Bartelt, Tom, January 12, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Barton, Martha, January 11, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Baungart, Gayle, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Beecey, Barbara, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Beecey, Barbara, May 25, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Bender, Julie, January 2, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Benjamin, Carol, June 1, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Bensinger, Frank, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Biggs, Dawn, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Binder, Pat, January 3, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Bhatt, Nilkanth, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Bolton, Janet, December 30, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Bolton, Vade, December 28, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Bonner, Ken, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Boster, Mark, December 24, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Boster, Gail, December 18, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Bouie, December 10, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Bouie, Bill, January 17, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Boyd, (Mrs.), January 11, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Bradley, January 14, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Bradley, Alakit, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Braunstein, Lesile, 2000s (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Bredeson, Dorothy, December 4, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Briggs, Anna C., January 30, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Brook, Louise, June 1, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Jean, December 27, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Bruce, Carol, 2000s (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Brunson, Leomia, January 19, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Bryant, Helen, 2000s (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Bugge, Diana, January 11, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Burton, Greg, December 21, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Butler, Larry, December 4, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Caldwell, Brain, May 24, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Callahan, Dave, January 2, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Callaghan, John V., January 12, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Camasda, Andrew, January 4, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Camosda, Andy, April 5, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Campbell, Marian, 2000s (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Campbell, Gray, January 10, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Carley, Stephanie, 2000s (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Carmen, Hirejdo, 2000s (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Carrigan, (Mrs.), January 10, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Chen, Anne, January 16, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Cherian, (Dr.), 2000s (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Christian, Prentice (Jr.), December 30, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Christman, Bruce, January 18, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Ciszek, Raymond, January 1, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Ciszek, Kathy, January 1, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Cleveland, Jim, May 27, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Codding, Rosemary, January 15, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Conyers, (Mrs.), December 17, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Coromellow, Gina, May 31, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Cosham, Ralph, December 4, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Cox, Peter, January 1, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Craft, D., January 8, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Craighill, Sherry Perkins, January 7, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Cramer, Brett, January 15, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Crowe, Jeff, June 5, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Crutchley, Michael, December 17, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Curich, Barbara, 2000s (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - D'Alesandro, (Mr.), 2000s (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Dadani, Norina, December 29, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Dawner, Richard (Sr.), June 5, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Karen, January 3, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Day, Jane, February 28, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Dearbarn, (Mrs.), June 2, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - DeCao, (Ms.), December 11, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - de la Fe, Mary, January 12, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - de le Fe, Sarah, June 5, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Deahl, Claudia Thompson, January 13, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Dellagiarino, Margie, December 29, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - DeNover, John, January 9, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - DeNoyer, John and Ann Csonka, 2000s (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Dix, Bob, December, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Dix, Robert B. (Jr.), January 8, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Dobberfuhl, Gail, January 9, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Donohue, (Mr.), June 7, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Dohaann, Eileen, January 19, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Donatuti, Pauline, December 19, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Drury, (Mrs.), January 17, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Edwards, Jan, January 5, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Elder, Jim, December 22, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Farrell, Theresa, May 11, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Fay, Evan, 2000s (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Fliess, Maurice, May 27, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Flynn, Thomas, January 12, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Forner, (Mr.), December 29, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Fox, (Mr.), June 2, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Foyle, (Mrs.), June 9, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Fraser, (Mr.), 2000s (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Fraser, Bill, 2000s (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Fraser, Christine, June 1, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Fraise, (Mr.), June 6, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Frohm, December 18, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Funk, Marianna, January 2, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Gallagher, Kevin, June 10, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Gernstein, Susan, January 8, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Gerstein, Bob, January 10, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Glenon, Elizabeth, 2000s (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Gonzalez, Leah, December 19, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Gordon, Leila, December 16, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Graves, Ellen, June 5, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Greenberg, Gail, January 7, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Greene, Vicki, January 16, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Grein, Tom, January 12, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Grillo, (Mr.), 2000s (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Grubisich, Tom, January 11, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Grubisich, Tom, December 11, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Grubisich, Tom, June 1, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Grubisich, Tom, January 2, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Guinea, (Mrs.), December 5, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Guinee, Barbara, January 15, 1998 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Guilfoyle, Sally and John, June 1, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Haas, David, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Hagelis, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Hagelis, Al, January 7, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Halpin, Julie, January 16, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Hannigan, Vera, January 28, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Harding, January 3, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Nancy, June 9, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Harris, (Ms.), December 19, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Hauser, Kathy, December 30, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Herold, Alda, May 16, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Hill, Bill, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Hindrichs, Wolf, May 30, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Hines, (Mr.), 2000s (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Hong, Grace, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Hotz, Peter, January 1, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Hous, Laura, December 29, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Howell, Janet (Senator), 2000s (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Hudgins, May 23, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Hunter, Carol, January 21, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Hunter, John, June 5, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Husch, Dennis, January 6, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Husted, Wesley R., 2000s (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Ingebristen, Karl, December 9, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Ingebristen, Karl, June 10, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Ireland, (Mrs.), December 18, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Ivan, Cole, June 9, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Jackson, Bill, January 12, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Jennings, Olivia, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Jetei, Judy, 2000s (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Jones, Suzi, 2000s (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Jones, (Mrs.), December 3, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Kain, George, December 28, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Kane, 2000s (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Kasprowicz, Joan, June 8, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Keefe, Bill, June 7, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Kelleher, Kenneth, 2000s (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Kendall, R., May 28, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Keith, Emily and Baba Freeman, May 28, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Kidwell, Fran, June 4, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Knapp, Liz, May 1, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - LaCroix, (Mrs.), January 12, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Lair, June 7, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Larson, Sarah, December 13, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Larson, N., December 10, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Larson, Sarah, January 16, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Leary, Joe, January 10, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - LeCesne, Alvarez, June 1, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Earl, February 5, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Susan, December 10, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Lilienthal, Philip, December 31, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Lilienthal, Philip, December 27, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Limar, Ann, June 8, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Loftis, James Goodwin, 2000s (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Lombardozzi, Lisa, 2000s (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Lordon, Diane, June 1, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Lucas, Cale, June 2, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Lundy, Mary, January 21 and February 5, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Lyle, Marilyn, March 30, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - MacIntyre, Pat, June 7, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Majette, Dean (Dr.), January 11, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Martin, Mike, June 5, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Martin, Michael, June 1, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Martin, Reid and Jill, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - McCracken, Jay and Pat, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - McDonald, Karen, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - McFalls, (Mrs.), June 8, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - McKnight, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Mcraken, Joanne, June 8, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - McVeigh, Joey, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Meader, (Mrs.), 2000s (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Mendelsohn, Stuart, January 9, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Mendosa, (Mrs.), June 8, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Adina, June 14, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Minnard, (Mrs.), May 31, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Moore, John, February 30, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Mobley, Kenneth, June 10, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Morgan, Debbie, December 15, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Morris, Nina, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Muir, Thomas, January 10, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Munroe, Kevin, January 20, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Murray, Mac, January 10, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Nicholas, Christian, 2000s (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Nicoson, W., May 31, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Nicoson, Patty, June 3, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Nicoson, Patty, June 3, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Nugent, Joan, December 9, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Olson, Shirley, June 2, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - O'Neil, Greg, January 22, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - O'Rooke, Tom, January 2, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Oswolt, (Ms.), 2000s (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Pace, Sandi, June 5, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Packard, Patty Kral, January 3, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Pennino, Martha, January 9, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Petersen, Lindsay, December 26, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Platt, Leslie, December 26, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Plum, Kenneth R. (Delegate), March 5, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Plum Ken, May 30, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Poppe, Robert, June 4, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Porter, (Mrs.), June 3, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Powell, Suzi, January 10, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Phillips, W.D. (III), January 12, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Principei, Frank, 2000s (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Pronske, Kurt, January 7, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Pronske, Kurt, 2000s (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Pyle, Robert (Mr. and Mrs.), December 19, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Ramsey, Nancy, December 11, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Randd, Guy, June 2, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Rando, Guy, January 8, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Ray, Martha, 2000s (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Rector, David, 2000s (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Rhea, Claud, June 14, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Rice, Kim, June 2000 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Robinson, David, December 29, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, David, January 11, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Rogersby, Martha, December 5, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Rudiselle, Suzanne, January 17, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Ruffin, Bernard, 2000s (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Rust, Thomas, January 13, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Sachland, Jack, March 25, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Salin, Dino, January 16, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Schambach, Pat, 2000s (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Schmid, John, January 11, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Schoka, Andy, May 18, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Schultz, Autumn, 2000s (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Schult, (Mrs.), December 16, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Scirah, John, 2000s (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Shchram, Sue, June 3, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Shubert, Kay, June 8, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Silvey, Marilyn, January 17, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Simon, Robert E., June 7, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Simon, Robert E., 2000s (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Simon, Robert E., January 16, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Simon, Robert E., January 1995 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Singer, Linda, June 1, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Slack, Connie, December 9, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Slaskel, Danny, January 3, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Claudia, November 1994 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Snowhite, January 24, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Spencer, (Ms.), January 8, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Spillane, Robert, January 5, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Stany, Charles, December 6, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Stapleton, Tim, December 18, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Stiebel, Joan, January 1, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Stout, Shannon, June 10, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Stowers, Joe, May 24, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Stowers, Joe, May 24, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Supley, Beth, December 20, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Taran, Nadia, June 5, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Terry-Todd, Teslene, February 16, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Thayer, Joan, January 17, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Thillmann, John, May 24, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Thomas, Howard and Margaret, June 7, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Thoesan, Richard, January 6, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Tierney, Leslie, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Toatley, Olivia, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Toohey, Sarah, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Trickett, Joy and Bessie, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Tsi, Mary Ann, May 24, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Tristyn, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Van Fleet, Paul, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Veatch, Chuck, June 4, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Vest, Bobby, November 27, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - VanVliet, (Mrs.), December 19, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Vincent, Marie, June 4, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Viray, Patrick, June 8, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Viray, Tina, June 6, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Vest, Bobby, November 27, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Vivona, Catherine, january 5, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Walcoff, Carol, 2000s (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Ward, Jeff, June 3, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Wengert, Vicki, January 3, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Weinberg, Fred, January 9, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Weinstein, Rosa, January 12, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Welsh, E., 2000s (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - White, Dr., 2000s (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Wicha, Carmen Gloria, December 7, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Wilhelm, Jane, December 15, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Wilkens, (Mrs.), 2000s (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Williams, Ed, January 1998 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Wingert, Victoria, January 15, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Wingert, Vicky, June 13, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Wilson, (Mrs.), 2000s (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Witherford, (Mrs.), December 26, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Wrighton, Bruce, 2000s (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Woods, Kris, January 1, 994 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Yarbrough, Edith, January 15, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Young, Robert, June 9, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Zter, (Dr.), January 6, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Series 3: 1996 Interviews (Volunteers), 1996, (6 boxes)
  These are additional transcripts and audiotapes that were done in 1996 by the students at Langeston Hughes Middle School. They were originally stored separated under the title oral history in the Planned Community Archives. They are now organized together with the rest of the Reston Reflections.
  - Aguero, Lloyd, April 28, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    464.1
  - Anselene, Susan, April 27, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    464.2
  - Babineau, Diane, May 4, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    464.3
  - Benton, Tom, May 21, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    464.4
  - Berman, Stephen, May 15, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    464.5
  - Bliss, Richard, April 13, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    464.6
  - Blitz, Cookie, April 26, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    464.7
  - Bollinger, David A., 1996 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    464.8
  - Bolston, Dan, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    464.9
  - Bouie, Bill, May 15, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    464.10
  - Bourn, Deacon, Rayford, May 12, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    464.11
  - Boyd, Margaret L., May 6, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    464.12
  - Boyd, Margaret, May 13, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    464.13
  - Colby, John C., 1996 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    464.14
  - Corey, Steven, June 2, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    464.15
  - Crutchfield, William E., May 15, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    464.16
  - Davidson, Judy, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    464.17
  - Decastro, Elizabeth, June 6, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    464.18
  - Delisio, Louis, May 15, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    464.19
  - Despins, Monica, May 21, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    464.20
  - Dix, Robert, May 6, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    464.21
  - Doolittle, Sara, May 11, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    464.22
  - Drachsler, David, May 7, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    464.23
  - Drewes, Jane, May 19, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    464.24
  - Eckert, Mary, May 5, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    464.25
  - Gerguson, Hal, May 8, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Fink, Dan, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    464.27
  - Foster, Kim, May 12, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    464.28
  - Fraser, Jim, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    464.29
  - Freer, Pam, May 21, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    464.30
  - Front, Chuck, May 16, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    464.31
  - Gatz, Donald, April 15, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    464.32
  - Gerdin, Donna, May 21, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 33)
    464.33
  - Gold, Rosalind, A., May 21, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 34)
    464.34
  - Goldberg, Benjamin, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    464.35
  - Grant, Pamela, May 3, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 36)
    464.36
  - Greenspan, Laura, May 14, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    464.37
  - Harroun, Sharon, June 14, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    464.38
  - Harroun, Sharon, May 7, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 39)
    464.39
  - Harwood, Beverly, May 19, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 40)
    464.40
  - Holmes, Gregory T., 1996 (Box 91, Folder 41)
    464.41
  - Jackson, Mary, April 24, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 42)
    464.42
  - Jackson, Mary, May 12, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 43)
    464.43
  - Volunteers, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 44)
    464.44
  - Jelinek, Pam, May 15, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    465.1
  - Jones, Pat, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    465.2
  - Jones, Suzi, April 27, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    465.3
  - Jones, Susan, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    465.4
  - Kain, George, May 2, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    465.5
  - Kane, Patrick, April 26, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    465.6
  - Karon, Shirley, May 13, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    465.7
  - Krebs, Joe, May 17, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    465.8
  - Larobardier, Fritz, May 9, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    465.9
  - Leary, Joe, June 9, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    465.10
  - Lena, Vic, May 21, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    465.11
  - Lilenthal, Lynn, April 22, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    465.12